http://www.armoury.co.uk/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Privacy Notice and PolicyAt Bathgate Limited T/A The Armoury of St James’s we recognise the importance of protecting your privacy, in line with our legal responsibilities. This notice is to advise you how we use any personal information you share with us, via our website. This notice also covers use of your personal information when you purchase, or are a recipient of goods and services purchased from The Armoury of James’s. Who we areThe Armoury of St James’s is the trading name of Bathgate Limited. Details can be found here: http://www.armoury.co.uk/contact Personal information we collectWe collect your personal information when you enter your details on forms on our website, when you contact us (in writing, by post, email, or posts and messages via the social media platforms that we support, or by phone). When you complete a ‘contact’, ‘enquire’ or ‘bulletin request’ form online, we may need to use your personal details to deal with your query or sales enquiry. The details may include your name, address, landline telephone/mobile number, and/or email and IP address.In the case of an enquiry on behalf of a company we may collect your company’s name; the company’s address, company’s email address and telephone number. How long we keep your personal informationWe use your personal information only to send you information you have requested from our company. Details of a purchase of goods or a service, and associated personal details will be retained no less than seven years. Purchases of services or productsWhen you purchase goods or a service, we will use your data to comply with HMRC rules. Hard copy sales and purchase invoices are retained off site in a secure location under lock and key. Why we collect your personal informationWe collect your personal information to: provide you with products and services that you may request from us; to check your identity to protect security, to prevent fraud and meet our legal obligations Storing your bank and payment card detailsBathgate Ltd is Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard (PCI-DSS) compliant. In plain English, this means we do not keep credit / debit details on file. Who we share your personal information with - third partiesYour personal information is only used by Bathgate Ltd T/A The Armoury of St James’s for the purpose(s) detailed above.We will share your personal information with authorities, (including the police, law enforcement agencies, credit reference and fraud prevention agencies and select other bodies), for:*the prevention and detection of crime*the prevention of fraud against Bathgate Ltd or customers*to prevent money laundering*for identity verification*for the purpose of legal proceedingsWe do not sell your personal information to any other third party, for any reason whatsoever. We do not use automated call services and we do not record telephone calls for training, or other purposes.In cases where your personal information has been passed to a third party as part of provision of a product or service purchased, you may need to contact the third party directly in relation to their continued use of your personal information. How we keep your personal information secureBathgate Ltd T/A The Armoury of St James’s is committed to keeping your personal information secure. All personal information collected via our website is stored on a secure server to protect it from being accessed or used inappropriately. How we keep your personal information accurateBathgate Ltd T/A The Armoury of St James’s will ensure that your personal information is kept accurate and up to date as far as is reasonably possible. We encourage you to advise of any changes to your information.Where you have opted-in to receive news we will use only relevant personal information to contact you. How to access your personal informationYou can access your personal information and your preferences at any time by contacting us http://www.armoury.co.uk/contactWe may communicate with you by email, post, phone, SMS text message and social media posts and messaging where you have provided consent at the time we collect your personal information. Updating your preferencesYou can change your personal information and marketing preferences at any time by contacting us http://www.armoury.co.uk/contactIf you do not wish to receive information by email from Bathgate Ltd T/A The Armoury of St James’s please use the unsubscribe feature on any promotional email received or use our ‘contact us’ form to request that your details are removed from our password protected database. In this case, we will only retain your personal information, where our legal or regulatory obligations require us to do so. Requesting a copy of your personal informationIf you wish to request details of personal information held on systems and in hard copy, please contact http://www.armoury.co.uk/contact Where we collect your personal information fromBathgate Ltd T/A The Armoury of St James’s collect your personal information:directly from you when you submit a Bulletin request on our website or face to facewhen you enquire about or purchase goods or a service; when we undertake a payment authorisation or when undertaking an identity checkwhen you purchase goods or a service; when shipments, parcels or post are handled by third party networks. Links to third party websitesOur website, emails and social media pages may contain links to websites operated by third parties. Bathgate Ltd T/A The Armoury of St James’s is not responsible for privacy notices, policies, services offered, or other site content displayed on third party websites. Changes to our Privacy Notice and PolicyWe review our privacy notice and policy regularly and will display the current version on this webpage. Last updated May 2018. How to contact usIf you have any questions about how Bathgate Ltd T/A The Armoury of St James’s is using your personal information, please contact usBathgate Ltd T/A The Armoury of St James’sRegistered in England number 234932517 Piccadilly ArcadePiccadillyLondon SW1Y 6NHContact email address: welcome@armoury.co.ukVAT number: 503380873Telephone: +44 (0) 207 493 5082Last updated: May 2018
Opening TimesMonday to Friday 10am to 6pmSaturday 12noon to 4pmClosed Sundays and Bank Holidays
The Armoury of St. James’s17 Piccadilly ArcadeLondon SW1Y 6NHUnited KingdomTel: +44 (0)20 7493 5082Fax: +44 (0))20 7499 4422Email: welcome@armoury.co.uk
Home
Top of page
Payment
Delivery
Terms and Conditions
Privacy Policy
Cookie Policy
